// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is generally used for performing tasks like creating the structure of the relations, deleting relation?",
    answer: "DDL(Data Definition Language)",
    options: [
      "DML(Data Manipulation Language)",
      "Query",
      "Relational Schema",
      "DDL(Data Definition Language)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following provides the ability to query information from the database and insert tuples into, delete tuples from, and modify tuples in the database?",
    answer: "DML(Data Manipulation Language)",
    options: [
      "DML(Data Manipulation Language)",
      "DDL(Data Definition Language)",
      "Query",
      "Relational Schema"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which one of the following given statements possibly contains the error?",
    answer: "select empid where empid = 1009 and Lastname = 'GELLER';",
    options: [
      "select * from emp where empid = 10003;",
      "Inselect empid from emp where empid = 10006;",
      "select empid from emp;",
      "select empid where empid = 1009 and Lastname = 'GELLER';"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What do you mean by one to many relationships?",
    answer: "One teacher can have many classes",
    options: [
      "One class may have many teachers",
      "One teacher can have many classes",
      "Many classes may have many teachers",
      "Many teachers may have many classes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A Database Management System is a type of _________software.",
    answer: "It is a type of system software",
    options: [
      "It is a type of system software",
      "It is a kind of application software",
      "It is a kind of general software",
      "Both A and C"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "The term 'FAT' is stands for_____",
     answer: "File Allocation Table",
     options: [
       "File Allocation Tree",
       "File Allocation Table",
       "File Allocation Graph",
       "All of the above"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: " Which of the following can be considered as the maximum size that is supported by FAT?",
     answer: "4GB",
     options: [
       "8GB",
       "4GB",
       "4TB",
       "10TB"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "The term 'NTFS' refers to which one of the following?",
     answer: "New Technology File System",
     options: [
       "New Technology File System",
       "New Tree File System",
       "New Table type File System",
       "Both A and C"
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Which of the following can be considered as the maximum size that is supported by NTFS?",
     answer: "4GB",
     options: [
       "Super",
       "Final",
       "Static",
       "Public"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Which of the following is a correct way to create an object of class Test? ",
     answer: "Test t=new Test();",
     options: [
       "Test t=new Test();",
       "Test t=new Test;",
       "t=new Test();",
       "new Test t;"
     ]
   },
  

  







];